<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Green Five</title>
    <description>This is the development blog for GreenFive, a story based FPS/RPG in the vein of SystemShock.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 01:40:52 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 01:40:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>FIRST</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I posted a new SuperEarlyPreAlpha build, and then had to post a new fixed version. There are only a few new additions to this
build: An animated health bar for the player HUD, and the first weapon is in the game now. The first weapon is just a metal pipe,
which is a little nod to SystemShock (the first weapon there was a lead pipe).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next step I plan on taking is to add some more complexity to the melee combat system. Right now there is only one attack type, a
simple swing attack. I plan to add a thrusting attack that can be used to push back enemies. There will also be a way to block damage.
There are also instantiated decals which need to be added. I also need to create a few more particle systems and find a few sound clips
so that striking different materials with the pipe will generate different sounds and cause different particles to be emitted at the
point of impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I may have found a way to address the lighting issues I’ve been having, if so I may include the next scene in the next build.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 07:24:12 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/greenfive/development/update/2016/03/28/FIRST.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/greenfive/development/update/2016/03/28/FIRST.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>greenfive</category>
        
        <category>development</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
